<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Australia Day on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Australia Day on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Stories</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/australian-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/australian-story/</guid>
      <description>One of the after lunchtime activities was reading an Australian story. For some classes this was a collection of tales from Aboriginal mythology and for others it was Edward the Emu by Sheena Knowles.
The Aboriginal tales were popular because they are told in very different way compared to European stories. They also seemed to enjoy learning about Aboriginal culture because it is unique and so distinct from that of Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet Game</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/alphabet-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/alphabet-game/</guid>
      <description>This was an activity based on The Alphabet Game game show (the Spanish equivalent was called Pasapalabra). It consisted of a quiz where you had to guess twenty-six words relating to Australia (one for each letter of the English alphabet). Each letter had an associated clue and players worked in teams. The first team to get all twenty-six words correctly is the winner.
For example:
 B: One of the colours on the Australian flag: Blue C: A popular sport in Australia: Cricket J: The name for a baby kangaroo: Joey  This activity was probably the most difficult for the students because they don&amp;rsquo;t know much about Australia yet and in order to find a words for a some of the more uncommon letters, like X, you have to choose something niche.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cricket</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/cricket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/cricket/</guid>
      <description>In the morning of the Australia Day celebrations the children played cricket against each other. I thought that cricket would be a good sport for children in primary school because it is non-contact, and relies more on making intelligent decisions and less on athletic prowess. This means that it should be enjoyed by a greater percentage of the students that sports where this is not the case.
Although cricket is one of the most popular sports in Australia, it is almost unheard of here in Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>