<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Australia Day on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Australia Day on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aboriginal Artwork</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/aboriginal-artwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/aboriginal-artwork/</guid>
      <description>Australia Day Celebration Aboriginal Artwork  1st, 2nd  Required materials:  Something to function as the mystery box (can be as simple as a folded piece of paper with a box printed on it or an actual box) Flash cards  Description: This is a game that is played in small groups. I found that four to five students was usually a good amount. Each person takes a turn being the one with the mystery box and puts a flash card of their choice in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alphabet Game</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/alphabet-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/alphabet-game/</guid>
      <description>Australia Day Celebration Alphabet Game  3 years old, 4 years old, 5 years old  Required materials:  A set of flash cards of any topic  Description: This is a game that is played with an entire class. It is intended to help reinforce the learning of certain words around the same theme. Examples of themes I have taught are:
 family members wild animals colours  Everyone stands in a circle and waits for the teacher to show a flash card and say a word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waltzing Matilda</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/waltzing-matilda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/waltzing-matilda/</guid>
      <description>Australia Day Celebration Waltzing Matilda  3 years old, 4 years old, 5 years old  Required materials:  A set of flash cards of any topic  Description: This is a game that is played with an entire class. It is intended to help reinforce the learning of certain words around the same theme. Examples of themes I have taught are:
 family members wild animals colours  Everyone stands in a circle and waits for the teacher to show a flash card and say a word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cricket</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/cricket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/australia-day/cricket/</guid>
      <description>Australia Day Celebration Cricket  3 years old, 4 years old  Required materials:  Colour flash cards A classroom  Description: This is a game that is played with an entire class. It is intended to teach very young children the colours in English. It involves the children finding something of a particular colour and showing you.
You start by choosing one of the flash cards and singing the following song (adjust the lyrics for the current colour, obviously):</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>