<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>El Peralejo School</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/el-peralejo-primary-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/el-peralejo-primary-school/</guid>
      <description>I was assigned to CEIP El Peralejo, which is a primary school (1st - 6th grade) and a pre-school (3 - 5 years old). It is located in Alpedrete, a small town in the mountains to the north-west of Madrid.
 I chose to live in the centre of Madrid rather than in Alpedrete, which was possible because the public transport is so good. Each morning I take the metro to the Intercambiador de Moncloa then catch a bus to Alpedrete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Experience</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/teaching-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/teaching-experience/</guid>
      <description>Assigned Classes and Subjects I was usually only assigned English classes. This is because El Peralejo is not a bilingual school, so the only subjects not taught in Spanish are French and English. My timetable was organised such that I did one English lesson each week with every class in the school. I liked this because it meant that I could spend time with all of the students, but it could also be challenging because it took me much longer to get to know them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Highlights</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/highlights-as-auxiliar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/assistant-portfolio/about/highlights-as-auxiliar/</guid>
      <description>Watching the Students Improve One of the biggest highlights for me so far has been being able to see the progress that the students have made in English. Even though I have only been here for about half a year, I can already see a difference between their skills at the beginning of the year and now. Many of the younger children have also gained a lot of confidence and they hardly ever greet me in Spanish anymore like they used to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>