<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Jesse&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What am I wearing today?</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/what-am-wearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/what-am-wearing/</guid>
      <description>Classes I did this activity with:  1st, 2nd  Required materials:  Cutout pictures of different articles of clothing  Description: This is an activity that is done in small groups. I found that two to four students was usually a good amount. Each person takes a turn to design an outfit using the cutout pictures, and the others have to say what someone in this outfit would be wearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mystery Box</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/mystery-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/mystery-box/</guid>
      <description>Classes I did this activity with:  1st, 2nd  Required materials:  Something to function as the mystery box (can be as simple as a folded piece of paper with a box printed on it or an actual box) Flash cards  Description: This is a game that is played in small groups. I found that four to five students was usually a good amount. Each person takes a turn being the one with the mystery box and puts a flash card of their choice in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What am I?</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/what-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/what-am-i/</guid>
      <description>Classes I did this activity with:  3rd, 4th, 5th, 6th  Required materials:  Hats for each student (I usually made/had the students make origami hats from sheets of newspaper) Animal flash cards  Description: This is a game that is played in small groups. I found that four to five students was usually a good amount. Each person puts on their hat and an animal flash card is sat in its brim, such that no one can knows the card that is in their hat, but can see those of their classmates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jumping Game</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/jumping-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/jumping-game/</guid>
      <description>Classes I did this activity with:  3 years old, 4 years old, 5 years old  Required materials:  A set of flash cards of any topic  Description: This is a game that is played with an entire class. It is intended to help reinforce the learning of certain words around the same theme. Examples of themes I have taught are:
 family members wild animals colours  Everyone stands in a circle and waits for the teacher to show a flash card and say a word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find something [insert colour here]!</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/find-something-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/find-something-blue/</guid>
      <description>Classes I did this activity with:  3 years old, 4 years old  Required materials:  Colour flash cards A classroom  Description: This is a game that is played with an entire class. It is intended to teach very young children the colours in English. It involves the children finding something of a particular colour and showing you.
You start by choosing one of the flash cards and singing the following song (adjust the lyrics for the current colour, obviously):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is Rat?</title>
      <link>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/where-is-rat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halleygen.github.io/auxiliar-project/portfolio/where-is-rat/</guid>
      <description>Classes I did this activity with:  2nd  Required materials:  The classroom pet (preferably one that is not and has not been alive) Various objects around which the pet can be placed  Description: This is an activity that I did with the entire class as a warm up. It is intended to help the children to learn how to use the prepositions of place in English. The two second grade classes had a class &amp;ldquo;pet&amp;rdquo;, a stuffed rat, who all the kids liked a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>